

PROFILE

I specialize in web content design, i worked for several years in a health services director, i also participate in front-end oriented web development projects.
I am in a continuous process of growth and learning, aimed at creating systems to improve other people's experience.

SKILLS

• HTML5 • GIT

• GitHub · CSS3

 Netlify · SCSS

• Figma JavaScript

 Adobe React.js

 Tailwind Photoshop

· Illustrator Node.js

EDUCATION

Grado, Ingeniería informatica 2023 - present

Codo a codo 4.0 Desarrollo web full stack Node.js 2024 - present

ComIT Google user experience (UX) 2023

Coursera Google data analytics 2023

LANGUAGES

- · Spanish Native
- English B1

BAITHAZAR GONZALEZ LOUREIRO FRONT END DEVELOPER

11/06/2002 Caba, Buenos Aires, Argentina. Balthagonzalez24@gmail.com www.linkedin.com/in/balthazargonzalezlou

EXPERIENCE

FREELANCE DEVELOPER

Web Developer 2023 - Present

· Html5, Css3, Scss, JavaScript, React.js, Tailwind, Node.js, GIT, GitHub Figma, SEO.

FREELANCE DESIGNER

Graphic Designer 2023 - Present

· Adobe Creative Cloud, Photoshop 2024, illustrator 2024, UnFold, Figma, Canva, Content Creator, Video Maker, Social Media.

OBRA SOCIAL DIGITAL

Web Developer and Designer 2022 - 2024

· Html5, Scss, JavaScript, React.js, Tailwind, Github, SEO, Adobe Creative Cloud, Figma.

MSBROKER

Web Developer and Designer 2021 - 2024

· Html5, Css3, JavaScript, SEO, Google Ads, Adobe Express, Figma, UnFold, Canva.